Love is so short, forgetting is so long.
All Too Well: The Short Film is a drama, music film directed by Taylor Swift.
Short film featuring the extended version of the
song “All Too Well” by Taylor Swift.
A troubled couple's romance blossoms before it eventually falls apart.
Her, played by Sadie Sink.
Him, played by Dylan O'Brien.
Her, Later On, played by Taylor Swift.
Him, Later On, played by Jake Lyon.
Her Dad, played by Shawn Levy.
His Friend, played by Rashauna Eastman.
All Too Well: The Short Film is a 2021 musical romantic drama short film written and
directed by the American singer-songwriter Taylor Swift in her filmmaking debut.
A film adaptation of her critically-acclaimed song "All Too Well" (2012), it is set against
the backdrop of the uncut, 10-minute version of the song released in 2021.
It stars Sadie Sink and Dylan O'Brien as a romantic couple whose up-and-down
relationship ultimately falls apart, compounded by their age gap.
Swift cited the works of Barbara Stanwyck, John Cassavetes, and
Noah Baumbach as artistic influences upon the film.
Produced by Saul Projects and Taylor Swift Productions, All Too Well: The Short Film was released on November 12, 2021, in select theaters by Universal Pictures
and on YouTube by UMG's PolyGram Entertainment and Republic Records, in conjunction with Swift's second re-recorded album, Red (Taylor's Version).
After a premiere at the AMC Theatres in Lincoln Square, New York City, it had a limited theatrical release in
major cities as well as special screenings at the 2022 Tribeca and Toronto film festivals.
It received critical acclaim, with particular praise directed towards Swift's direction as a
debut filmmaker as well as the acting, script, drama, and production values.
The film garnered several awards and nominations from music and film organizations, including an American Music Award, a Hollywood Critics Association Award, an Art Directors Guild Award and a Grammy Award for
Best Music Video; at the 2022 MTV Video Music Awards, it won Video of the Year and Best Direction, making Swift the first artist in VMA history to win Best Direction for a self-directed work.
The film explores themes of music video, break-up, love affair,
heartbreak, boyfriend girlfriend relationship.
The tone is emotional.